HAREL PANKER

WEB DEVELOPER / UI DESIGNER

PORTFOLIO

panker.io/

GitHub: github.com/harelpanker

CONTACT

+43 677 63721016

www.linkedin.com/in/panker-harel/

Email: harelpanker@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am a driven, hardworking, web developer, who is looking to expand my skills and knowledge in the world of development and design.

My focus in the past two years has been building websites for private clients, mainly using Webflow.

The ideal workplace offers me the opportunity to contribute, yet it also allows me to face challenges and learn.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER | 2018 - PRESENT

- Usage of Webflow to develop websites for clients which include e-commerce, portfolios, and blogs
- Specialization in SEO (Search Engine Optimization)
- Enhancement of websites using UI/UX strategies
- Usage of HTML, CSS (Scss), Javascript, and Javascript Libraries
- Experience working with WordPress
- Knowledge in React
- 2019/2020 Working on projects at "Krieger des Lichts" in Nürnberg, Germany

ISRAEL AIRPORT AUTHORITY

BEN GURION AIRPORT, ISRAEL | 2018

SECURITY WORK

ISRAELITISCHE KULTUSGEMEINDE WIEN| 2012 - 2013

MILITARY SERVICE

ISRAELI DEFENSE FORCES | 2008-2012

- "Duvdevan" counter-terrorism unit
- Medic and Sergeant

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE

Technion-Institute of Technology, Israel | 2017

LL.B. - BACHELOR OF LAWS - GPA OF 88 OF 100

Ono Academic College, Israel | 2013-2017

PSYCHOMETRIC EXAM - General score 646

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA - GPA of 85 of 100

SKILLS

- HTML
- css/scss
- JavaScript
- React
- Next.js
- SEO
- Material-UI
- Styled-components
- Webflow
- WordPress

LANGUAGES

- Hebrew Native
- English Advanced
- German Novice